Right now, if this candlestick just
shoots to the [__] moon, we'll turn
the 10,000 into like 40.
>> Okay. All of it. All it going down. It's
going down. Here.
>> Pull out. Pull out. Pull out.
>> If I lose my money, I will be I will be
>> The market opens in 8 minutes.
>> Okay. Open the right now.
>> I see.
>> Wow.
>> Here we go. It's got a bunch of cars out
here. This guy knows what he's doing.
This guy This is the guy.
>> This guy definitely knows what he's
doing. We just walked here where
>> from uh literally a mile down the road.
All right. So So this is Alex and uh
Alex is one of the world's uh top
leading day traders. So I have no clue
what I'm doing and he's going to show me
the ropes today. We're going to turn
$10,000 into a million in one day.
>> Yeah. Maybe.
>> Are we worried about the market opening?
Cuz it opens in
>> No, it's open. It's open.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So the market already opened but it's
not 8 yet.
>> Yeah. So, they opened that like Sunday
5:00 p.m. EST, but there's no real
volume. Now is when the volume starts
kicking in.
>> Okay.
>> So, now
>> the volume's already k. So, people are
making trades already
>> right now. Yeah. I see. I see. I see.
So, we missed out on $300,000.
>> I was expecting like 700 computer
screens.
>> I mean, you you only need one.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't cuz I was thinking like whenever
I get my trading set up, I was going to
have like 18 of them.
>> I mean, that does not make you more
money. It's just
>> really I was thinking like like more
screens, more money. Like you can watch
the the NASDAQ and the 401k and the
>> There's nothing.
>> Okay, I see. So, I have $10,000.
[Music]
>> Sorry. I actually have zero clue what
I'm doing at all. I thought this would
be an interesting video cuz Alex has How
long have you been doing this?
>> Probably like 7 years now.
>> Oh, damn. Okay. Could I figure this out
in 2 to 3 months?
>> No. Sure.
>> Okay. Yeah, cuz I was going to just like
dump all my money into it like one day.
You
>> would have lost it.
>> Really? I mean, you could, but you're
going to lose it all.
>> Cuz I felt like the less you care about
the money, the more you get it.
>> Once you know what you're doing, you got
to know what you're doing first.
>> Every time I would gamble, it was like
the less I cared.
>> Yeah.
>> But I did lose it all still. So, what's
your whole set and forget thing, by the
way? That's put your money in and leave
it. Right.
>> Yeah. You just put it set for I did the
opposite. I like set and remembered and
then pulled it all out the next like we
will need that by the end of today.
Maybe.
>> I mean, that's why I have this here just
in case you
>> lose the money.
>> That's perfect. This is literally
perfect. If we lose this, there's
another emergency $10,000.
>> And you just keep putting the money in
until you eventually make money.
>> Really? Okay.
>> So, right now it's it's 804. So,
realistically,
>> we're 4 minutes late.
>> So, we have two trades that we can
possibly enter, right?
>> NZD JPY, which is the New Zealand dollar
versus the Japanese yen for buys. We
want this to continue going to the
upside because we're at a strongly area
of interest. We created a double bottom
and the daily time frame is creating a
dogee above the EMA, rejecting previous
structure point. And then the weekly has
created the weekly retracement on
previous structure as well. The only
thing I don't really like is that the 1
hour hasn't really retested how I
wanted. So we could go into a little bit
of draw down.
>> Just a little bit of draw down. Are you
okay with that?
>> Yeah, that's sounds good.
>> But like are you okay with being a draw
down?
>> Draw down. Your money's draw down.
>> Yeah. Your money's going to go into a
little bit negative.
>> Yeah, that's draw down. Yeah.
>> Okay. But if your money goes negative,
you can't
>> pull out. You got to set and forget.
>> Just it'll come back.
>> Maybe. I don't know. There's a there's a
there's a 70% chance.
>> Okay. Yeah. I feel like you don't think
we need more computer screens.
>> No.
>> Why are you concerned about that?
>> I'm just worried. I feel like I would
have like a screen to watch like the
>> the news or something.
>> These are the mug shots for Alex
Gonzalez and Sebastian Rivera.
>> If we would have entered the trade 30
seconds ago, we'd be in draw down right
now.
>> So, that's not good.
>> It's normal.
>> Draw down is normal. You don't want draw
down to happen. Draw down isn't good.
But it it's unavoidable.
>> Okay.
>> Are you okay with being in draw down?
I'm going to take whatever advice you
have,
>> but if I lose my money, I will be I will
be angry. So, like, how much is how much
different is this from like the Wolf of
Wall Street?
>> Very different.
>> That was, bro, that was a scam. What do
you mean?
>> All right. So, how much money have we
made so far?
>> No, we haven't taken We haven't taken
the trade. We could hypothetically enter
this shirt right now, but we might enter
some draw down. I want you to be okay.
>> Okay. I'm I'm down for whatever as long
as there's no risk of losing it. No,
there's a 100% risk of losing.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. It's just it's a less
chance of losing.
>> Okay. Okay. Let's maybe we start with
like5 or $6.
>> No, no. We're never going to make
anything.
>> Okay. All of it. All in.
>> All in. All right. So, we're going to
buy NZD JPY.
>> What is this?
>> So, we are pre-calculating our risk
right now. So, we're going to be trading
NZDPY million dollar account. Our our
risk is going to be usually I was going
to do maybe 100K, 150K. So, we're going
to do 110K. 100,000 mine. really
>> 10,000 years.
>> Putting 100 grand in right now.
>> 110.
>> Okay.
>> We're betting against the Japanese yen.
>> So, that right there is our position
size in. This is our lot. That's what
we're going to calculate here on the
phone. NZDPY. We're going to click
trade. We're going to put our lot size
90. And then our stop loss is this
number that's down over here. So, you
see right now, if we would have entered
5 minutes ago, we would have been in
more drops.
>> We're buying $20,000 worth of I don't
even know what right now. I don't even
know. He just put 100,000 of his money
in. I put 10,000 of my money in. That
was my last 10,000. We're buying. You
want to wait.
>> Okay. Yeah. Just click the buy. Buy.
Buy. Buy.
>> Okay. We're in.
>> That's only 20% of the position.
>> Wait. So, we just bought We just lost
$300.
>> That's just the cost of doing the trade.
That's normal.
>> It cost $300 just to put our money in.
>> Yes. That's normal, bro.
>> Oh my god.
>> Buy again. Okay. Wait. You got to buy it
in batches.
>> Yeah. So, we don't pay that much in
fees.
>> Okay. I see.
>> So, we're technically right now 700
bucks.
>> Oh my god.
>> Sell it. No, bro. No. No. No. No. We're
down. No. No. We're down four grand
right now. It's okay. It's all right.
Trust me. Just trust the bosses, bro.
This is normal.
>> Cody, set and forget. You're not
forgetting. You remember.
>> No, it's only 1,000.
>> Okay.
>> Now, we just wait. This is like the
boring part of this [__]
>> How long do we wait?
>> 3 hours? 4 hours?
>> So, we just got to sit here for 3 hours
and watch.
>> I mean, usually this is where I just go
do [__]
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> And you just come back and maybe you
lost. Oh, I'm I'm checking on my phone
as I'm doing [__]
>> So, like you're So, like you're doing
things but stress.
>> No, I I I set and forget.
>> So, Okay. I see. So, you don't care.
>> This can literally fly straight to the
stop loss and we're just taking another
trade. Look, we're up 1,500 bucks.
>> Okay. Sell sell. No, no,
>> tell. Get out.
>> No. No. No. Look. Right now, we're down
six grand. But it's okay. That's normal.
Trust me.
>> I'm going to pull up.
>> You pull up. Pull up.
>> No. No. I'm pulling up my trading app.
This is the app I use.
What is that?
>> Robin Hood.
>> You have nothing.
>> You have zero.
>> Look. Look. I put $40,000 in. So I have
lifetime. I'm up.
>> No. No.
>> You put five grand in and you withdrew
$48 in profit.
>> Like when do you decide to remember
again?
>> Whenever it hits stop loss or take
profit.
>> Why you stressing, bro? We're in profit.
We're in profit.
>> It's going down. It's going down. Here.
>> You got You look like you're stressing,
bro. You got to chill. Come on.
[__] bro. This guy's stressing me out,
bro.
>> Are we Are we up? Are we good,
>> dude? We're up four, dude. I don't know
why he's tripping.
>> Perfect. Look at he's trying to look at
the door, bro.
>> What the [__] is he doing, bro? What the
hell is wrong with this guy?
>> 3,000. I don't
>> Oh, no.
>> Sell it.
>> No.
>> No. No. We got to wait, bro. It's only
been 20 minutes. See, we're up back up
right now.
>> Okay, we are up $7,000. Okay. Well, you
went outside. Everything remained
perfectly fine.
>> Oh my god. Here we go. And I'm the
target. That's great. I am now the
target for this animal.
>> You ready?
Oh, that was a good one. Yeah, that was
good. Oh, yeah. They Oh, that's a good
bite. Oh my god. Oh, that was tough. Oh,
yeah. Slide your arm out. You want to
slide?
>> Let's go. Let's go.
>> Let the arm slide out, Cody.
>> Good boy,
>> dude. He came at it.
>> Oh my god. No. No. That was good.
>> Okay.
>> I was just looking at how strong I am.
>> Oh yeah,
>> dude. They need to hand See, that's what
I'm saying. They need to hand these out
to criminals when they escape prisons.
Cuz every time a prisoner escapes
prison, the dog is just going to make
them bleed everywhere. They get bit.
>> Yeah, it's a bad thing.
>> Like every prisoner needs one of these
arm things because like it's it's bad
for like it's not good for the people
when the dog bites.
>> An hour and a half, maybe two. Brad, you
got to stay calm.
>> I'm perfectly calm.
>> Oh no. I don't think you know how much
we're up right now.
>> Holy [__] bro.
>> Oh my god.
>> Yo, it was actually here like a second.
>> No way. It's shooting, dude.
>> I know. I know. I know. I know.
>> Pull out. Pull out. Pull out. Sell.
>> No. No.
>> Wait. This is crazy. We're up 70 grand.
>> No, bro. That's what I'm talking about.
>> We're up 70 grand. So, yeah. Guys, you
all need to pick up day trading. Put all
your money in right now. I'm tell
>> specifically this scenario.
>> Follow the candlesticks. Follow the up
up trending charts.
>> You got to get educated first, bro. You
got to learn. Like, I have a strategy. I
didn't just [__] guess this [__]
Well,
>> you don't want to be in front of the
computer cuz then your emotions get in
place. You've been a little bit
emotional, lately, bro. Earlier, if
you're emotional,
>> I feel like if you ignore your emotions,
you could lose money. No,
>> you got to like your You got to let your
emotions kick in.
>> No.
>> And tell you when to stop.
>> The market right now has no idea we're
even in this position. So, why you going
to let the emotions factor into that?
>> Sell it. Sell it when it gets to here.
>> That would be break even. You would make
zero money. You want to close out
minimum up here?
>> So, wait. You're telling me
theoretically we can let this get to 20
grand. We sell it, reinvest in another
trade, double that, and keep repeating
the process toward a million.
>> Yeah. It takes like 45 days.
>> I don't have that much time. We're going
to go on a spin.
>> Yeah. All right. So, right now we're up
probably 60,000.
>> He's going to let me borrow the Porsche
and we're going to have fun for a little
bit while we're letting our money stack.
The idea is to let your money work for
you, right? Like we could be doing hard
labor, but instead the idea is
mentality, success, and money
>> and set and forget.
>> Let them let your emotions control your
actions. No, no, no, no, no. Let the
market do it.
>> The money.
>> Don't attach emotions to the market.
>> Exactly. That's Wall Street for you.
>> You got it.
>> All right. Sweet.
>> Forget to set.
>> Oh my god.
Are you filming?
>> Yeah. Just keep it. Just keep it in a
gear.
Pick a gear.
Heat.
[Music]
All right. Uh, we just went on a drive.
We went we had some lunch and uh, where
are we at? How's it looking? Tell me,
give me the rundown. Give me the
lowdown.
>> So, we're at the highs where we wanted
to be basically by this time.
>> We're where he said we would pull out.
>> We're literally at So, we were up
>> at 89,000.
>> No, 90,000 now.
>> We're at 90. Oh, we're at 90. Yeah, but
we were I saw it on the phone.
>> 91 92.
>> No, but we were at like 99. I saw it
when we were at
>> 93. So, should we pull out at 100? Is
our goal 100? Do you think we'll hit it?
>> No, this is going to go more than 100
for sure. Really?
>> Yeah. This is probably going to be like
400 g. No, for sure. 100%. But it's
going to take two to 3 days to get
there.
>> I see. So, I don't know. You could wait
it out or
>> What do you How do you know?
>> I mean, I just know, bro. I don't know
how to explain it.
>> How do you know? What does he know? What
does he know?
>> The daily time frame has the daily wick.
We're having the bullish engulfing. We
rejected from the structure. And now if
the daily closes like this in the next
four hours, it just has destined to
continue going to the upside. If right
now we're at a one to one and we're only
at one to one, bro, we can easily have a
$5 $600,000 trade. Just getting started
on the continuation.
>> You're telling me,
>> bro? Did you even pay attention?
>> You're telling me if I would have
brought a million dollars,
>> it would be at five. Yeah,
>> I would have $5 million.
>> Well, if it right now, you would be at
two. Yeah.
>> Well, you would be at 900.
>> I feel like I lost even though I won.
Like I feel like I lost. I should have
bought
>> like I should have liquidated
everything.
>> I thought you were going to do that. So
I mean we have a decision to make. You
can either close right now because
basically after 12:30 which in in the
next 8 minutes
>> it's going to go into a neutral.
>> It's going to go into a slowdown. So we
can close the positions or I'll close
your position. I'm going to continue to
hold
a second.
This is the perfect area for it to do
two things. Either break above or
completely reverse.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean look at it. Last time
it was there, it went down.
>> So, we're there again. It could go down
again.
>> I don't like this. But you you have
confidence it's going to go back down.
>> 50/50.
>> Okay.
>> I just wanted to hit like 500 today.
>> There's not enough momentum. Like that's
it from 12:30 in the next 8 minutes.
>> The next 8 minutes is when it could
drop.
>> No, it's just going to it's just going
to stand still. It's going to basically
do what it did right here.
>> How does he know what it's going to do?
I have 8 minutes to decide whether or
not I want generational wealth or
mediocre wealth.
>> Well, the most you'll probably get out
of this is like 30 40 grand. But not
today.
>> Out of 10.
>> M. Well, I I don't have time, man. I
need money now. I'm stressing him out so
much he has to use the stress.
>> He's using that to cope with me. Look,
you're you're at 95,000.
>> 95.
>> I don't think it's going to go past
that, bro. I think 90 is like the high.
You We can get You can get 9,000 and
that's it. Done for this.
>> Really? It is 95. Pull out. Pull out.
Pull out. Pull out. No, no, no. It's
dropping.
>> No. No. No. No. No. This is amazing.
This is amazing news.
>> It's like cheating.
>> Wait. Wait. Okay, I changed my mind. Put
it back in.
>> You closed it. Look. 9,200.
>> No, put it back in. I want to make more
money.
>> No, you already closed the position.
>> You doubled your money, dude.
>> Dude, you
>> I didn't double. I fell so short. Do I
have to pay taxes on that?
>> Yeah, of course.
>> Oh my god. Move it to the offshore
account. So
>> now we're good.
>> I'm going to take the 19 grand and buy
more screens.
>> That's not going to make you more money,
bro.
>> Literally.
>> I I promise you if you were to have more
screens, you would have lost money
today.
>> All right. Well, uh, today was a massive
success. As you can see, um, the stock
is plummeting. Wow.
>> Having a minor retracement. I mean,
that's what you
>> a retracement. That's how he copes with
the loss.
>> That's how I cope with
>> a minor retracement. You just lost $80.
So, uh, now the pile of cash grows. The
idea is to turn this into a million
dollars. What do we do next?
>> We wait until tonight and we do it
again.
>> You think this is the best way to make a
million?
>> 100%.
>> Literally. So, I shouldn't go invest it
in anything else.
>> What are you going to put 19 grand into?
>> German Shepherd breeding farm. I don't
know. Thanks for helping me today. Of
course,
>> we're going to turn this into a million
dollars. I have one final question
before we go. Okay.
>> I was curious genuinely uh if you wanted
to uh invest in my hedge fund.
>> Your hedge fund?
>> Yeah.
>> Who's trading your hedge fund?
>> I me.
>> You
when how much do you need?
>> Uh hedges are averaging like 500 bucks
each.
>> And then what do you make a monkey?
>> Uh depends on how many hedges I sell.
Like if someone's doing a yard, like a
bigger yard.
>> Oh, wait. Hedges?
>> Yeah. You like bushes? Yeah.
>> Oh, not like a tree.
>> No, I have to buy a bunch of hedges. I
have a a landscaping company. So, like I
I would put like hedges all around, but
it depends how many hedges I sell. Like
in the spring, I'll sell a lot more.
>> Good luck with your hedge fun.
>> Thank you, dude.
>> Good luck. Appreciate you. All right.
Good luck.
>> Thanks.
>> Good luck.
>> I just I'm worried about a drought cuz
like all the hedges will die. Uh
>> I think it'll be fine.
The hedge fund.